Upcami
Here we go...it's up-cam! This time with Saya Eguchi from Beyonce and Subway,
Beyonce, and Minami Okamura of Ameagari Kawakai.
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs. I, Eguchi, met all the members for the first time in a while the other day,
It had been quite a while since we had all worked together, so we didn't have much contact with each other, so when we met in person, we didn't exchange much more than a "good morning" or "good afternoon".
So when we met in person, we kind of said good morning.
I didn't really get a sense of the distance between us, but when we talked, we were able to have a good time as usual.
But when it had been a while and there was a gap between us, my shyness was triggered.
But I've always been a little bit shy to begin with.
That's right, we get along well when we see each other every day.
But if you see each other every day, you get to know each other well.
No, no, no, it's only for 10 days or so, right?
Yes, I was a little surprised myself.
I didn't realize it at all.
There was a time when I didn't realize it.
I, Okamura, fell down for the first time in 5 or 6 years.
Yes, I fell down and scraped my knee.
It was the first time since I became Beyonce, so it's been five or six years.
The last time I fell down, my mother would disinfect me as soon as she got home.
It was small.
But I had a big enough scar that a normal bandage wouldn't work anymore.
You lived boldly, didn't you?
Yes, so I had to go out and buy a bandage, disinfect it, and patch it up by myself.
It was probably the first time in my life.
It hurt a little bit, but all I could do was laugh.
I was like, "Why did I fall down when I grew up?
It was really funny.
If I was in the middle of a concert tour, there was a possibility that it might have affected my performance.
But now I'm taking a break.
I still think the timing was good.
I feel like I've had a good life experience.
I have to be careful in my life.
I'll be careful.
Okay, so let's start with this up-dated paper.
I have to go! Making of the music video shooting
It's a solo song by Akari Takeuchi from Angulum's newest single
I have to go! Please take a look at the making of the music video for "I have to go!
The view from the view.
Yes, okay.
Yes, I have to go! music video shooting has begun.
This time I am alone, so I miss all the members very much already now,
But I hope to make it through the day.
I am shooting in a very beautiful place, so I want to enjoy my time alone and have fun. I will do my best.
Thank you for watching.
The dream began as a child again
The road that has continued for as long as I can remember.
The concept of this music video was to create a solo song for Ms. Takeuchi.
As it is a solo song by Ms. Takeuchi
I wanted to show the charm of Ms. Takeuchi's unpretentious personality and free performance.
and her free performance
I thought it would be good to show those aspects of Takeuchi's personal music video
I thought it would be a good idea to showcase
I thought of a project like this.
When I had the opportunity to shoot Angstrom before
when we had a free dance performance in a mirror-mirror
I was really impressed by Takeuchi's energetic and cool dancing
I had a great impression of her.
I was very much impressed by the lyrics of the song, "I like to sing and I like to dance.
I was very much impressed by the way Takeuchi-san danced so vigorously and coolly.I think Mr. Takeuchi hit on the point that
I think that Takeuchi san's charm that I felt was hit upon.
I asked her to dance freely at the end of the song.
Also, the song had a sense of speed.
the running scene, etc.
Ms. Takeuchi's energy
I wanted to add a sense of strength to the song.
I'm sure you must have gone through a lot of frustrations in this activity.
I thought about all the frustrations she must have gone through in her life
So I decided to mix in some darker scenes.
Yes, please give me some sound.
Yes!
I'm getting embarrassed.
I did the steps for this.
The last step.
Tumble down.
You don't have to get on it.
I drew this for you right now.
The future.
The future...
It's shining right here.
Yes, sir! Let's go.
Here we go.
Let's go!
One, two, three, four.
I just want to see your face.
Just a little bit.
A little more.
It's a big relationship.
That's right.
12345. - Yes, cut.
Okay, let's keep it in the same position and let's go for the snowstorm.
Okay, here we go.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
Okay, cut.
I want to show you what I see in my eyes on this day.
I want to show you the view
Without showing it to anyone
I sang it over and over
I'd do it all over again
To the me of that day
I'm showing you now
The future I dreamed of
The future... The future...
It's shining right here.
Cut! Thank you very much.
There's a big wave happening.
There's a big wave happening
Big wave is happening
A big wave is happening
A big wave is happeningA Big Wave is Happening
A Big Wave is Happening
A big wave is happening
I have just finished shooting the music video for my solo song, "I gotta go! which will be included in the new single to be released on June 14.
We really shot it in the morning at the beach,
Recently, Anju's music video shoots outside have been either rain or strong winds, but today it was sunny and I was very happy,
I was very happy that it was sunny today.
But the strong wind was still there.
I don't know why I have such a good luck with wind,
But we had a great time shooting this morning, and there are many highlights,
I hope you will enjoy watching it.
Bye bye!
The sea and the scenery are so beautiful, and Takeuchi-san's bright smile is so wonderful,
There were a lot of scenes with free movement, which is what we usually do when we shoot music videos,
In our usual music video shooting, there are dance scenes and lip scenes with hands on the camera,
I thought it would be very difficult because I have never shot a scene where we move freely in a room.
I, Okamura, heard this song for the first time at Akari Takeuchi's graduation performance at Yokohama Arena the other day,
It was the first time I heard Ms. Takeuchi in her red and blue dress singing this song, and it is a really wonderful song, as well as the lyrics and melody that only Takeuchi-san can sing.
I have always felt that Takeuchi-san's straight, high-pitched voice is also very attractive,
I have always felt that Takeuchi's straight, high-pitched voice is also very appealing, so I really felt the charm of this song, and it has become my favorite song.
This is the "making of music video shooting of Akari Takeuchi's solo song, "I have to go! The making of the music video shooting".
I'm sorry for the things that happened.
Nasagi
I love you
Angelem Dousousou on sale now!
Thank you for all your hard work!
Here is the next one: Beyonce Vocal Recording for Yozora no Yume wo Yawakurenai Yozora ni
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Yuhane Yamazaki for Beyonce's newest single "Yomeshinai yokozora ni" (I can't even draw a dream).
Now I would like to record it sequentially.
There is a part I want to specify,
As you are you, please take one breath after this.
One breath until "It's wonderful to be born.
Yes, okay.
I won't let you be the night sky I can't even dream of.
I'll walk while humming the melody you love
I won't let you be the night sky that can't even sing of love
It's wonderful that you were born as you
Yes, it's perfect.
It's like she's talking to him.
It's like a Chinese play in a musical.
It's like a Chinese musical play.
There's a child actor in the cast.
It's like you're leaving it up to the child actor.
It's like you're telling the story in that way.
Please give me another one like that.
I won't let the night sky become a place where you can't even dream
I'll walk while humming the melody you like
I won't let the night sky where I can't even sing of love
It's wonderful that you were born as youIt's wonderful that you were born as you.
Eight lines of A melody 1A dash treatment. Let's go here.
I won't let you be the night sky I can't even dream
So many stars love you
I can't draw anything, even when I can't believe it
Don't forget that you were born on such a beautiful star
Yes, OK!
So much... love.
Lou is okay, that's the feeling
Don't forget you were born on such a beautiful planet
Let's just take a breath.
So, even when you don't believe it
So, please keep it in the sigh
I'm going to take a breath from there
Thank you for watching.
I won't let the night sky be a place where you can't even dream
So many stars love you
I can't draw anything, even when I can't believe it
Don't forget that you were born on such a beautiful star
Yes, OK, I'll take it.
Next is the B melody of the first song.
Thank you, sorry, take care, bye-bye
Words disappear, the stars are full of thoughts, I want to hold them all in my arms
Please tell me you are going to sing the next song in your dreams.
Now, let's go to these 4 songs.
Don't forget that you were born on a beautiful star
Thank you, sorry, take care, bye-bye
I want to embrace all of them
In a dream
Yes, it's good. And you should know this part once too.
Thank you, sorry, take care, bye-bye
Don't forget you were born on a beautiful planet
I want to hold them all in my arms
Let's have it now
Now, let's continue with the first chorus
Even a dream can't come true, the moment I'm here now
I'm taking a breather here, too.
You and I are sharing a song. It's a miracle.
Miracle, it's a miracle, too... extend it by two and cut it by three.
Okire run, full of thoughts, I want to hold it all in my arms
Even my dreams can't come true, the moment I'm here now
You and I are sharing a song, it's a miracle
Yes, okay. Stretch it out a little shorter, okay?
It's a miracle. One, two, cut.
And right after that, la-la-la-la-la, the cart's in.
Here we go.
I want to hold it all in my arms
Even a dream can't come true, the moment we're here now
You and I are sharing a song. It's a miracle.
That's all.
That's all I have to say.
I think this song by Beyonce, "Can't Even Dream in the Night Sky," is a very charming number with straightforward lyrics and a spectacular arrangement by the brass band.
I was watching the recording of the song, and it is a song with many repetitions of the same melody, so you have to change the way you sing the song for each scene.
So you have to change the way you sing in each scene to keep the flow of the song.
I was impressed by her precise pitch and rhythm, and when she performed "Beyonce", I could see the penlights in the audience were lit up with stars.
When you perform "Beyonce", the penlights of the audience look like stars, and it is a song that moves me while I sing it.
I felt that I would like to perform it again with even more feeling.
This was the vocal recording of Yuha Yamazaki for "Beyonds Yume no Don't Even Draw a Dream".
You can do it!
With Saya Eguchi of Beyonds SubwayBeyonds Saya Eguchi of Subway and
Beyonds Upcoming paper by Minami Okamura of Rainy Morikawa Sea
Here's the next one
Tsubaki Factory: Seventh Blossom Continuation Vocal Recording
Seventh Blossom Continuation from Tsubaki Factory's music
Please take a look at the vocal recording of Riko Yamagishi and Saori Oda!
Okay, let's take some pictures, shall we?
It's a little bit like a cute girl's heart, a little bit like a maiden's.
Let's do it with that in mind.
Okay, let's start with the first A melody.
Let my fingertips play with the shells of my gumshiro.
Boring spring, isn't it?
I'm so embarrassed by the gloss
I'll pretend I didn't hear the message as best I can
The rhythm is a little slow, so I'll chop it a little more finely.
And the melody at the top of my head, the shell of a gumshoe
I'll pretend I didn't hear the rest, but that's the best I can do
Stand up in the GE
I let my fingertips play with the shell of a gumshoe
I say it's a boring spring
I'm so ashamed of my gloss
I'll pretend I didn't hear the rest
It's the best I can do to send a message
OK, I'll take it now.
Here comes the first chorus.
It's raining.
It's time to take me with you.
Seventy-fifth bloom continues.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I'll be your girlfriend
I'll make love to you and spill it
Why is this color a joke?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I don't know. I don't know.
I think it's good.
Is it obvious? Give me a break.
I'm in love with someone who's obviously in love.
I just want to ride a little bit backwards.
It's like you want to ride a little bit behind.
It's so obvious that I want to ride in the back.
Love that's so obvious
Well, it's just a little bit.
I'll give it a try.
It's raining on Sunday.
Take me back to my place...
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I'll be your girlfriend... if you do this with your voice.
Why are you joking about the color?
Okay, that's good. Let's continue.
But my favorite part...
I can't even drive like that.
I don't love you. I don't even like you.
A crush I feel only for you.
I feel like I'm not in love with you.
What I need a little accent
I don't like the way you just feel.
Be careful with the pitch.
One more! Take two.
But my favorite partBut my favorite part
It's so frustrating to smile.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm so sad to see you go.
Buka.
You were singing earlier.
Suddenly I don't know what's going on.
Faintly fading
What's that?
Yes, it is.
Right? Are you all right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
May I take this?
Okay, one more.
But my favorite part.
"The frustratingly smiling, seven-part honesty.
I can't even drive like that.
I don't love you, I don't love you
A crush I feel only for you
Yeah, this one's okay.
Okay, I got a good one.
I guess we're done then.
Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'll start with the first A melody.
Also, there's a little bit of pitch.
I'll go ahead and start there.
Boring spring, isn't it?
I can't do that part.
I'm sorry.
I just can't get it.
I've heard it a hundred times.
It's a boring spring.
Spring, spring, spring, spring, spring...
It's spring, isn't it?
Spring, spring, spring...
It's here, isn't it?
Gumshoe, the shell of a gumshoe... Let me play with your fingertips.
What can I say? It's a boring spring!
I'm so embarrassed, Gloss. I'm pretending I didn't hear you.
It's the best I can do.
Oh, yeah, let's do it here.
Message, message, message
Just a little light. Message.
That's a good idea.
I'll let you play with the shell of a gumshoe with my fingertips
It's a boring spring, you say.
I'm embarrassed to say it's a boring spring Gloss, pretend you didn't hear me
It's the best I can do.
You say you're throwing it away, but then you put an edgebosom in the third line.
It's quite a lyric, isn't it?
It's like she's throwing it away.
It's like he's calculating everything.
It makes you want to poke your head in, doesn't it?
Like, "You're not going to put that in there.
It's like, "I feel better when I can sing.
That's a good comment.
Let's go to the chorus.Let's go rusty then!
Rain forecast for Sunday
It's time to take me home!
Seventh bloom continues
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
I'll be your girlfriend
I'll make love to you and spill it
Why is this color a joke?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it's a nice touch of love.
It's a little more spring-like
A little more like...
Tarararararararararararararararararararararararararararararar...
Seventh bloom continues
It's got a little bit of a groove to it, doesn't it?
I want it to have a bouncy, bouncy feel to it.
And also... at the beginning...
The pitch of "It's about time...
It's about time, about time, about time...
That's the part that needs work.
You know, the obvious love.
It's all behind the scenes.
I can't do the obvious love thing. I can't do it.
A little bit of rhythm there.
Yes, sir.
Rain forecast for Sunday, Sunday, Sunday.
It's time to take me with you.
Seventh bloom continues
I'm in love with someone who knows I'm in love with you.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I'll be your girlfriend
I'll make love to you and spill it
Why is this color a joke?
I'll go put it in.
I'm gonna put in a lot of stuff.
I'm going to put something in it.
I don't hate it. I don't hate it.
I don't hate it.
It's like they can see right through you.
It's like, "Oh, I'm sure he'll put it in there somewhere.
Like, "Use it.
I think it's good.
I think I want to take another one.
Let's take another one.
Okay.
Rain forecast for Sunday, Sunday.
It's time to take me away.
Seventh Bloom Continues
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
I'll be your girlfriend
I'll make love to you and spill it
Why is this color a joke?
That's good, that's perfect.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
I thought it was a very cute and delicate song.
Both Ms. Yamagishi and Ms. Onoda expressed themselves in different ways.
Both of you have different expressions in your voices, and I thought they were both very beautiful.
Yes, it was.Yes, sir.
You know, Beyonce, she's usually a little more energetic.
She's not like a strong girl.
We are what we are..." kind of music.
So when I listen to Tsubaki Factory's songs
I always get the image of a girl who is fragile and wants to rely on someone
Like a girl who is fragile and wants to rely on someone.
We've never done that kind of expressive work before, so
I thought it would be very difficult.
I thought the recording video was a great learning experience for me.
(This is a continuation of "Camellia Factory: Seven Minutes to Bloom")
This is the vocal recording of Riko Yamagishi and Saori Onoda.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
I wouldn't kiss you okay
I couldn't even tell you
Pride Bright July 12 On Scion
It's going to be good.
It's time to say goodbye to the up-dated paper brought to you by Saya Eguchi and Minami Okamura!
I watched a lot of videos this time, but I was most impressed by the recording of Tsubaki Factory's song "Shichibunsaki no Tsugi" (Continuation of the Seven Minutes Blossom).
I haven't heard this song live yet.
I haven't heard this song live yet, but as Saya-chan said earlier, the delicate pitch and the rhythm seem to be unexpectedly detailed and difficult, so I'd like to see how it changes in a live performance.
I, Eguchi, was impressed by the making of Akari Takeuchi's music video for the song "I have to go.
I was really moved when I saw it at the Yokohama Arena concert, but the music video gave me a different, bright and positive impression, and I want to see more of it.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse of what you don't normally see.
This time, Upkami's partner is Sayu Eguchi of Beyond Subway,
and Minami Okamura of Beyond Amagamigawaumi.
Good bye.
Next time on UPKAMI,
Juice-Juice Pride Bright Making of Music Video Shooting
And,
and the recording of "Ai no Kedamono" by Anjelum.
Please look forward to it!